It was rather interesting just to watch them gathering their materials and bouncing around, what do they call it, kangaroo walk or something like that.
Who named it that?
I don't know.
I bet those men are going to get quite a reception when they get back to Earth.
Yes, I'll be so glad when they land back now, but I think that's pretty well a fact because they've landed so many safely now.
I feel relieved. Just getting off of the Moon was the thing that was...
Have they met with the one that was circling?
Yes, they've rendezvoused. So I understand. That wasn't shown either, but they say they have rendezvoused.
So that's a matter of making the circles and then coming down.
What do you sort of imagine for the future? Do you imagine them sending a...
I think they will. I think they will.
We'll do some more exploring up there, because that was such a very small area, when you think
of it, that they just gathered rocks and, oh, samples of soil and all, and they did
a probe for some samples, and just what was going to come of that, I don't know, I'd
be glad to read it.